Victor Vargas

Full Stack Web Developer

Montreal, QC - (514)-377-2518 - Victorvaflo@gmail.com

Experienced web developer with a passion for creating innovative web solutions. With 2 years of experience in web programming, website design, and project management, I have worked with a variety of clients and projects. My technical skills include programming languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, and frameworks like React and Vue.js. I also have experience in optimizing websites. My project management experience includes planning, organizing, and implementing successful projects using tools such as Trello, Jira, and Asana. My goal is to provide effective and customized web solutions for each client, using my technical skills and creativity to meet the specific needs of each project.

Technical Skills

	Javascript/TypeScript, Node Js, Html, C/C++, C#, Java:se/ee, Swing, Css, Android, Php, React, Jquery, Python, Ruby, Vue.js
Database	MySql, MariaDb, PostgresSQL,SqlLite, Redis
IDE	Visual Studio Code, Android Studio, Visual Studio, Neat Beans, Eclips
Other	Git, Trello, Aws, Jira, Jenkins, Putty, FileZilla, Aws

Work Experience

Full Stack Web Developer

2021-2022

illuxi, Montreal, QC

- PHP Full Stack Developer.
- Quality Assurance Developer.
- Design and Development of New Web Components, Templates, and Pages.
- Provided customer support via Crisp.

Full Stack Web Developer

2022-2023

Synex performance d'affaires (illuxi), Montreal ,QC

- Full Stack Developer using Vue.js and Ruby .
- Proficient in optimizing code for better performance.
- Design and Development of New Web Components, Templates, and Pages.

Education

High School Diploma

2012-2017

Antoine de Saint-Exupéry-Montréal

Web Programming and Development, Certificate of Collegial Studies (ACS) Institut supérieur d'informatique -Montréal

2019-2021